adsimilate.com 2014-08-29

# Privacy Policy : PPC : Online Ads : Pay Per Click Advertising : Adsimilate.com

| 

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies only to websites that are owned and/or operated by or on behalf of Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information about you as you utilize any Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. services, including the adverting services we provide to businesses that have their own web sites (our "Advertising Network"). Please be advised that our Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. By using services provided by Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. you indicate that you agree to the collection and use of your information by Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**Why Information is collected**  
Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. collects information to improve the services we provide and to present you with information and features that will interest you. We also use your information to measure our success and performance. For example, aggregate information gives us an idea of the number of visitors we attract and how they navigate our site. Personal Information We Collect: Any personal information that is collected by us is provided by you strictly on a voluntary basis. We may receive personal information from you in a number of ways, depending on the Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. service you are using and your choices while using our services. Depending upon the nature of the service being provided, we may ask you for, and you may choose to send to us, your name, e-mail address, physical address or other personal information necessary to complete a transaction or provide services to you. For example, if you choose to run an advertising or publisher program through Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc., we will need to collect certain personal information about you in connection with administering the program; however, we do not collect any personal information from site users in connection with our activities on sites in our Advertising Network. Wherever we ask you for personal information, we try to include a link to this Privacy Policy for your review.

**Use of Personal Information**  
As noted above, unless you voluntarily provide personal information for a specific purpose, we do not collect personal information from you. We will never combine any personal information about a user of our site with any aggregate information we collect about that user, whether collected on our site or our Advertising Network. If you choose to provide personal information, we use your personal information to provide you with particular services that you request. For instance, we may use your personal information to contact you about advertising services that you have requested and to provide you with data about your advertising campaign. We may also share your personal information with business partners who provide services you have requested. In these cases, we will provide only the information that is needed to perform the service. If you do not want Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. to share your information in this way, you can simply choose not to sign up for the service in question. By providing your email address to Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc., you expressly consent to receive emails from us.

Adsimilate Marketing, Inc. does not sell, trade or rent personal information to other companies. However, we will transfer personal information in connection with a sale or merger of Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. or the division responsible for the services provided to you. We may also share your personal information with our technical consultants, third party auditors and other third parties who make our site available, enhance its functionality or provide associated services and/or who deal with you in processing your orders and/or delivering content, samples, products, services and gifts and prizes. These third parties are not allowed to use personal information except for the purposes of providing the applicable services. In addition, we may provide information to law enforcement authorities or pursuant to a court order or to investigate suspected fraud. Our site and services are maintained in the United States of America. By using the site and/or services, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy.

**Aggregate Information We Collect and Use**  
In addition to personal information, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as site pages viewed, browser type, computer information, cookies, clickstream data and other information. This aggregate information is analyzed and combined with similar aggregate information of other users and may be collected both on our site and on other sites in our Advertising Network. Such aggregate information is anonymous and does not identify any individual user. We may share aggregate information with our business partners and other third parties.

"Cookies" are small data files that are sent to your browser and are stored on your hard drive, keeping track of your general activity on a site. When you make subsequent visits to our site or another site on our Advertising Network, your cookie gives us a summary of your preferences and past experiences on the site. This allows us to tailor Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. services to your needs. Your cookie may be altered at different times throughout your visits to a site, and it is updated frequently as you use various Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. features and services. When you use the services of Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. or our partners, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookie. You can and may opt-out and set your browser to reject cookies; however, this may affect some functions of this site and our other services.

"Clickstream data" is a trail of electronic information that is left at each web site you visit. This information can be collected and stored by a site's server. Clickstream data is used to tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use, the address of the site from which you linked to our site, how much time you spend on each page of our site, how you navigate throughout the site.

**Other Web Sites**  
The Adsimilate Marketing, Inc. site may link to advertisers and other sites that collect personal information about you when you leave Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. and that may have privacy policies and practices that are different from ours. This type of collection or use of information is beyond Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc.'s control and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every site you visit before providing any information. These sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Since we do not control these sites; we are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such sites.

**Security**  
Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. stores all data using industry standard security devices, such as firewalls and encryption protocols, to prevent against unauthorized access to our data. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. We have put in place policies to restrict access to your information by our employees. However, Adsimilate Marketing, Inc. cannot guarantee that your information will be completely protected from unauthorized access and you assume such risk when you use our services.

**Corrections or Removal of Personal Information**  
This site gives users the following options for changing, modifying or deleting information previously provided. Users can email [support@adsimilate.com](mailto:support@adsimilate.com). Users can send mail to the following postal address:

Phone: (315) 944-0873  
Fax: (315) 679-5013  
E-mail: [support@adsimilate.com](mailto:support@adsimilate.com)

Adsimilate Marketing, Inc.  
P.O. Box 2434  
Liverpool, NY, 13089

We are not responsible for removing your personal information from the lists of any third party who has been provided your information in accordance with this policy.

**Protection for Children**  
This is not a web site directed to children under the age of 13, and Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. does not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age from our website. If you are under 13 years of age, do not send any information about yourself to Adsimilate Marketing, Inc., Inc. We have no intention of collecting personal information from children under the age of 13. When we become aware that personal information from a child under 13 has been collected without such child's parent or guardian's consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**IP Addresses**  
An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer or network when you are on the Internet. When visitors request pages from our Web Site, our servers log the visitor’s IP address. We may collect IP addresses for a variety of internal purposes, such as system administration, to report click data information to our business partners or to audit the number of visits to different pages on our Web Site.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Be sure to visit this page frequently to find any updates we have made. Your continued use of the site after such changes have been posted indicates your consent and acceptance of such changes.

**Effective Date**  
This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on November 9th, 2009.

|  |   
---  
| 

**Adsimilate Community**  
Adsimilate Marketing, Inc is excited to announce the launch of our new proprietary ad platform! [Adsimilate Community](http://www.adsimilatecommunity.com/) brings you targeted and low cost traffic to make your online marketing a success. Experts in PPC search engine marketing, remarketing, display advertising and online marketing. We offer the best service and solutions to suit your business needs.  

**PriceAndShop.com**  
We are proud to announce our new shopping comparison website! Please visit [www.priceandshop.com](http://www.priceandshop.com/) to find the best prices on products from national retailers before you buy! Also, visit our[ facebook page](http://www.facebook.com/PriceAndShop)!   

|
